YOU ARE FRIENDS
THAT WOULD BE
DOING A LITTLE
BIT. IT'S GONNA
BE THE POP
OUT. SO I
SLIP. OKAY, EVENTS
AND NEW JERSEY.
I THINK WHAT
YOU CONNECT WITH
A BUNCH OF
PEOPLE IT'S ALWAYS
LIKE ENDLESS. YOU
KNOW ME. IT'S
SO MANY TALENTED
PEOPLE IN THIS
DUDE IF YOU
FIND A LIKE
GOOD GROUP OF
PEOPLE THAT'S YOU
KNOW THAT GENUINE
ENERGY. IT'S NOT
A HARD PART
OF IT EXACTLY.
OKAY, OKAY. WOULD
YOU SAY YOU
GO OUT MORE
AND NEW JERSEY?
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M SAYING? I
FEEL LIKE JERSEY
GOT A LOT
GOING ON OVER
THERE. PEOPLE DON'T
KNOW ABOUT YOU
KNOW WHAT I
MEAN? LIKE TALENTED
PEOPLE PEOPLE THAT
STARTED DOING NEW
SHIT FIND DIFFERENT
VIBES IT'S A
LOT MORE THAN
OUT HERE THAN
PEOPLE THINK PRETTY
SMART MAN. YOU
KNOW THAT SHIT